I heard you
used to live in a big mansion,
sleep in a big bed,
with pretty chicks all around.
Now you're scrubbing toilets for us.
Does it feel good?
Mr. He, why so quiet?
Do you think
talking to people like us is beneath you?
Still putting on airs with me?
Who do you think you are?
A son-in-law of the Wen family.
You're just my dog here!
Get a problem?
Clenching your fist, want to hit me?
Come on, hit me! Hit me!
Screw you!
You wanna fight?
Eat dirt!
What are you doing?
Sir,
we're doing the public a favor.
This guy? Let me tell you:
he used to cheat and bully people,
commit all manners of crimes.
We're just teaching him a lesson,
for doing good for society
and getting rid of an evil for the people.
Looks like you want to get tased again.
No, no, no.
We're just kidding, just kidding.
Stand straight!
You, come with me.
Sir, have you met my people?
Is the money enough?
If not, I'll have someone send more.
As long as you take good care of me,
there will be plenty of benefits for you
in the future.
Go in, Mr. He.
What?
Who are you?
Wh- What are you doing?
He Mu wants to bribe us.
Wishful thinking.
Boss, I found it.
Wen Yan didn't die back then.
That car accident was faked.
The one cremated was
an unidentified female corpse.
Not only did she not die,
but she was also hidden in Wenshan Group
by Wen Yanhui.
[Personnel Adjustment of
Wenshan Group]
Wenshan Group announced
a major personnel adjustment today:
Wen Jianan,
granddaughter of Chairman Wen Yanhui,
[Dearest: Episode 15]
has officially returned to the group.
It is reported
that she and her grandfather
will jointly promote
the highly anticipated
Xingji Entertainment Complex
development project.
Industry insiders analyze
that this move marks
the official entry of
the third-generation successor
into the core management of Wenshan Group.
Ayan, look.
The group is getting better and better
under my management, isn't it?
If the land of Xingji
can be successfully developed,
its status in Xinggang
will be untouchable.
You told me back then
that the group's success owed to you
and without you,
I would be nothing.
Ayan,
I kept you alive just so
you can see
that I can do better than you
with your own eyes.
I am the real master of the group.
Dad, you're back.
My dear dad.
Come have a drink with me.
Drinking like this all day,
you are really hopeless.
Dad,
but today is the anniversary of
Mom's passing.
Don't you miss her?
Don't you always say
that Mom is your favorite?
But why?
Why do you never allow me to
visit her grave to pay my respects?
Your mom is buried in hometown.
A long journey from here.
Besides, paying respects isn't
about formalities.
As long as she is in your heart.
Besides,
after this drink,
sober up tomorrow.
The Wens shouldn't behave like this.
Got it.
My dear dad.
Have a drink with me.
I'll have Ahao make a copy.
Mom.
Mom, I'm Wen Xin.
Xinxin.
My Xinxin, Xinxin.
For so many years,
you've been locked up here by him.
The beast,
I'll kill him.
Time's running out.
Let's go.
Mom, we'll get you out of here.
Go.
Jianan,
my child.
Mom finally gets to see you.
I finally get to see you.
So,
I'm the child you had with Wen Yanhui.
For all these years,
he locked you up here
and forced you to give birth to me.
I'm sorry, my child.
For all these years,
you've both suffered so much.
Why are you apologizing?
You didn't do anything wrong.
It was that damn Wen Yanhui
who ruined your life.
We'll get you out of here.
Let's make that man pay the price.
I can't leave. I can't leave.
Why?
Once he finds out the truth,
he will do whatever it takes.
He could persecute me then
so he can do it to you now.
I'm not afraid of death
but I can't watch you
suffer because of me.
But we can't just leave you here.
I've been here for over twenty years.
A day more or less doesn't matter to me.
Xinxin,
you've been holding on
all by yourself for so many years.
I know all.
Now,
you're not alone finally.
Jianan,
I'm sorry
for I missed your childhood.
But I can be your weapon since I'm here.
When Wen Yanhui is brought to justice,
when everything is over,
we three can finally reunite.
Okay?
Okay.
Next,
just do as I say.
Okay.
You've been through a lot.